Guide to the E. L. Wolven Glass Plate Negative Collection, 1897-1944
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series V. Drama, Music and Dance, 1900-1936
  - Second Hall Play — "Urfaust,", 1927 Mar 11-12 (Box 62/63 [202_03])
  - Second Hall Play — "Urfaust,", 1927 Mar 11-12 (Box 62/63 [202_05])
  - Second Hall Play — "Urfaust,", 1927 Mar 11-12 (Box 62/63 [202_06])
  - Second Hall Play — "Urfaust,", 1927 Mar 11-12 (Box 62/63 [202_07])
  - Second Hall Play — "Urfaust,", 1927 Mar 11-12 (Box 62/63 [202_08])
  - Second Hall Play — "Urfaust,", 1927 Mar 11-12 (Box 62/63 [202_11])
  - Second Hall Play — "Urfaust,", 1927 Mar 11-12 (Box 63 [203_13])
  - Second Hall Play — "Urfaust,", 1927 Mar 11-12 (Box 63 [203_22])
  - Second Hall Play — "Urfaust,", 1927 Mar 11-12 (Box 63 [203_23])
  - Second Hall Play — "Urfaust,", 1927 Mar 11-12 (Box 63 [203_24])
  - Founder's Day play — "Inkle and Yariko,", 1927 Apr 29 (Box 72/73 [220_03])
  - Founder's Day play — "Inkle and Yariko,", 1927 Apr 29 (Box 72/73 [220_04])
  - Founder's Day play — "Inkle and Yariko,", 1927 Apr 29 (Box 72/73 [220_05])
  - Founder's Day play — "Inkle and Yariko,", 1927 Apr 29 (Box 72/73 [220_06])
  - Founder's Day play — "Inkle and Yariko,", 1927 Apr 29 (Box 72/73 [220_07])
  - Founder's Day play — "Inkle and Yariko,", 1927 Apr 29 (Box 72/73 [220_08])
  - Founder's Day play — "Inkle and Yariko,", 1927 Apr 29 (Box 72/73 [220_16])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 81 [236_05])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 81 [236_06])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 81 [236_21])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 84 [Box240_020])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 84 [Box240_022])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 84 [Box240_023])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 84 [Box240_024])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 85/86 [Box242_001])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 85/86 [Box242_002])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 85/86 [Box242_003])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 85/86 [Box242_004])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 85/86 [Box242_005])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 85/86 [Box242_006])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 85/86 [Box242_007])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 85/86 [Box242_008])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 85/86 [Box242_009])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 85/86 [Box242_017])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 86 [Box243_023])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 86 [Box243_024])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Duenna,", 1927 May 13 (Box 33 [Box264_020])
  - Sophomore Party — A large group of students costumed as Ku Klux Klan members in the "Southland" scene in the "The Matchbox Tour," a skit show presented by the Class of 1930 to the Class of 1931. The students are in white robes and hoods, and there is a sign that reads "Klu Klux Klan,", 1927 Oct 22 (Box 66 [208_01])
  - Sophomore Party — A large group of students costumed as Ku Klux Klan members in the "Southland" scene in the "The Matchbox Tour," a skit show presented by the Class of 1930 to the Class of 1931. The students are in white robes and hoods, and there is a sign that reads "Klu Klux Klan,", 1927 Oct 22 (Box 66 [208_22])
  - Sophomore Party — A large group of students costumed as Ku Klux Klan members in the "Southland" scene in the "The Matchbox Tour," a skit show presented by the Class of 1930 to the Class of 1931. The students are in white robes and hoods, and there is a sign that reads "Klu Klux Klan,", 1927 Oct 22 (Box 66 [208_23])
  - Sophomore Party — Boston scene in the "The Matchbox Tour," a skit show presented by the Class of 1930 to the Class of 1931. Two of the students are costumed as Harvard students, 1927 Oct 22 (Box 66 [208_24])
  - Sophomore Party — California scene in the "The Matchbox Tour," a skit show presented by the Class of 1930 to the Class of 1931, 1927 Oct 22 (Box 66 [208_10])
  - Sophomore Party — California scene in the "The Matchbox Tour," a skit show presented by the Class of 1930 to the Class of 1931. The chorus members are holding pick axes, 1927 Oct 22 (Box 66 [208_21])
  - Sophomore Party — Full cast of the "The Matchbox Tour," a skit show presented by the Class of 1930 to the Class of 1931, 1927 Oct 22 (Box 66 [208_25])
  - First Hall Play — "Magda,", 1927 Dec 3 (Box 79 [232_01])
  - First Hall Play — "Magda,", 1927 Dec 3 (Box 79 [232_02])
  - First Hall Play — "Magda,", 1927 Dec 3 (Box 79 [232_03])
  - First Hall Play — "Magda,", 1927 Dec 3 (Box 79 [232_04])
  - First Hall Play — "Magda,", 1927 Dec 3 (Box 79 [232_05])
  - First Hall Play — "Magda,", 1927 Dec 3 (Box 79 [232_06])
  - First Hall Play — "Magda,", 1927 Dec 3 (Box 79 [232_08])
  - First Hall Play — "Magda,", 1927 Dec 3 (Box 79 [232_09])
  - First Hall Play — "Magda,", 1927 Dec 3 (Box 79 [232_10])
  - First Hall Play — "Magda,", 1927 Dec 3 (Box 79 [232_11])
  - First Hall Play — "Magda,", 1927 Dec 3 (Box 79 [232_16])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84 [Box240_011])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84 [Box240_012])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84 [Box240_013])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84 [Box240_014])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84 [Box240_015])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84 [Box240_016])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84 [Box240_017])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84 [Box240_018])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84 [Box240_019])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84/85 [Box241_006])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84/85 [Box241_007])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84/85 [Box241_008])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84/85 [Box241_012])
  - Second Hall Play — "The Yellow Jacket,", 1928 Mar 9-10 (Box 84/85 [Box241_013])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1930, 1928 May 14 (Box 32 [Box263_006])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1930, 1928 May 14 (Box 28 [package155])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1930, 1928 May 14 (Box 28 [package155b])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1930, 1928 May 14 (Box 28 [package155c])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1930, 1928 May 14 (Box 28 [package155d])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1930, 1928 May 14 (Box 28 [package155e])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1930, 1928 May 14 (Box 28 [package155f])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1930, 1928 May 14 (Box 28 [package155h])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1930, 1928 May 14 (Box 28 [package155i])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1930, 1928 May 14 (Box 28 [package155j])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1930, 1928 May 14 (Box 28 [package155k])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_001])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_002])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_003])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_004])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_005])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_006])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_007])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_008])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_009])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_010])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_011])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_012])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_013])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_014])
  - Third Hall Play — "Lorenzo the Magnificent,", 1928 May 21 (Box 46 [Package42_015])
  - Sophomore Party — Scene from "Mariposita," Act I of "The Sophomoric Sophistries of 1931," a skit show presented by the Class of 1931 to the Class of 1932, 1928 Oct 27 (Box 65 [206_11])
  - Sophomore Party — Scene from "Mariposita," Act I of "The Sophomoric Sophistries of 1931," a skit show presented by the Class of 1931 to the Class of 1932, 1928 Oct 27 (Box 65 [206_12])
  - Sophomore Party — Scene from "Mariposita," Act I of "The Sophomoric Sophistries of 1931," a skit show presented by the Class of 1931 to the Class of 1932, 1928 Oct 27 (Box 65 [206_15])
  - Sophomore Party — Scene from "The Man with the Green Whiskers," Act II of "The Sophomoric Sophistries of 1931," a skit show presented by the Class of 1931 to the Class of 1932, 1928 Oct 27 (Box 65 [206_07])
  - Sophomore Party — Scene from "The Man with the Green Whiskers," Act II of "The Sophomoric Sophistries of 1931," a skit show presented by the Class of 1931 to the Class of 1932, 1928 Oct 27 (Box 65 [206_08])
  - Sophomore Party — Scene from "The Man with the Green Whiskers," Act II of "The Sophomoric Sophistries of 1931," a skit show presented by the Class of 1931 to the Class of 1932, 1928 Oct 27 (Box 65 [206_09])
  - Sophomore Party — Scene from "What, No Watermelons," Act III of "The Sophomoric Sophistries of 1931," a skit show presented by the Class of 1931 to the Class of 1932. Behind a chorus of dancers, a number of students are in blackface and costumed as "washerwomen, cotton pickers, [a] blackberry vendor" and fishermen, 1928 Oct 27 (Box 65 [206_10])
  - Sophomore Party — Scene from "What, No Watermelons," Act III of "The Sophomoric Sophistries of 1931," a skit show presented by the Class of 1931 to the Class of 1932. Behind a chorus of dancers, a number of students are in blackface and costumed as "washerwomen, cotton pickers, [a] blackberry vendor" and fishermen, 1928 Oct 27 (Box 65 [206_13])
  - Sophomore Party — Scene from "What, No Watermelons," Act III of "The Sophomoric Sophistries of 1931," a skit show presented by the Class of 1931 to the Class of 1932. Behind a chorus of dancers, a number of students are in blackface and costumed as "washerwomen, cotton pickers, [a] blackberry vendor" and fishermen, 1928 Oct 27 (Box 65 [206_14])
  - First Hall Play — "Arms and the Man,", 1928 Dec 7-8 (Box 80/81 [235_01])
  - First Hall Play — "Arms and the Man,", 1928 Dec 7-8 (Box 80/81 [235_02])
  - First Hall Play — "Arms and the Man,", 1928 Dec 7-8 (Box 80/81 [235_03])
  - First Hall Play — "Arms and the Man,", 1928 Dec 7-8 (Box 80/81 [235_04])
  - First Hall Play — "Arms and the Man,", 1928 Dec 7-8 (Box 80/81 [235_05])
  - First Hall Play — "Arms and the Man,", 1928 Dec 7-8 (Box 80/81 [235_07])
  - First Hall Play — "Arms and the Man,", 1928 Dec 7-8 (Box 80/81 [235_08])
  - First Hall Play — "Arms and the Man,", 1928 Dec 7-8 (Box 80/81 [235_09])
  - First Hall Play — "Arms and the Man,", 1928 Dec 7-8 (Box 80/81 [235_17])
  - First Hall Play — "Arms and the Man,", 1928 Dec 7-8 (Box 80/81 [235_21])
  - First Hall Play — "Arms and the Man,", 1928 Dec 7-8 (Box 80/81 [235_22])
  - First Hall Play — "Arms and the Man,", 1928 Dec 7-8 (Box 80/81 [235_23])
  - Goodfellowship Club play — "Daddy Long Legs," presented by Vassar employees, 1929 Feb 16 (Box 85/86 [Box242_011])
  - Goodfellowship Club play — "Daddy Long Legs," presented by Vassar employees, 1929 Feb 16 (Box 85/86 [Box242_013])
  - Goodfellowship Club play — "Daddy Long Legs," presented by Vassar employees, 1929 Feb 16 (Box 85/86 [Box242_014])
  - Goodfellowship Club play — "Daddy Long Legs," presented by Vassar employees, 1929 Feb 16 (Box 85/86 [Box242_015])
  - Goodfellowship Club play — "Daddy Long Legs," presented by Vassar employees, 1929 Feb 16 (Box 85/86 [Box242_016])
  - Goodfellowship Club play — "Daddy Long Legs," presented by Vassar employees, 1929 Feb 16 (Box 86 [Box243_002])
  - Goodfellowship Club play — "Daddy Long Legs," presented by Vassar employees, 1929 Feb 16 (Box 86 [Box243_004])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped,", 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_002])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped,", 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_003])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped,", 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_004])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped,", 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_005])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped,", 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_008])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped,", 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_009])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped,", 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_011])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped,", 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_012])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped,", 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_013])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped." Two of the clowns in the production are in dark makeup of an unidentified color, 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_001])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped." Two of the clowns in the production are in dark makeup of an unidentified color, 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_006])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped." Two of the clowns in the production are in dark makeup of an unidentified color, 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_007])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped." Two of the clowns in the production are in dark makeup of an unidentified color, 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_010])
  - Second Hall Play — "He Who Gets Slapped." Two of the clowns in the production are in dark makeup of an unidentified color, 1929 Mar 15 (Box 51 [Package59_014])
  - Shakespeare Play — "A Winter's Tale,", 1929 May 13 (Box 50 [Package56_002])
  - Shakespeare Play — "A Winter's Tale,", 1929 May 13 (Box 50 [Package56_003])
  - Shakespeare Play — "A Winter's Tale,", 1929 May 13 (Box 50 [Package56_006])
  - Shakespeare Play — "A Winter's Tale,", 1929 May 13 (Box 50 [Package58_001])
  - Shakespeare Play — "A Winter's Tale,", 1929 May 13 (Box 50 [Package58_002])
  - Shakespeare Play — "A Winter's Tale,", 1929 May 13 (Box 50 [Package58_003])
  - Shakespeare Play — "A Winter's Tale,", 1929 May 13 (Box 50 [Package58_004])
  - Shakespeare Play — "A Winter's Tale,", 1929 May 13 (Box 50 [Package58_005])
  - Shakespeare Play — "A Winter's Tale,", 1929 May 13 (Box 50 [Package58_006])
  - Third Hall Play — "The King's Henchman,", 1929 May 17 (Box 72/73 [220_01])
  - Third Hall Play — "The King's Henchman,", 1929 May 17 (Box 72/73 [220_02])
  - Third Hall Play — "The King's Henchman,", 1929 May 17 (Box 72/73 [220_10])
  - Third Hall Play — "The King's Henchman,", 1929 May 17 (Box 72/73 [220_13])
  - Third Hall Play — "The King's Henchman,", 1929 May 17 (Box 72/73 [220_14])
  - Third Hall Play — "The King's Henchman,", 1929 May 17 (Box 72/73 [220_17])
  - Third Hall Play — "The King's Henchman,", 1929 May 17 (Box 72/73 [220_20])
  - Third Hall Play — "The King's Henchman,", 1929 May 17 (Box 72/73 [220_21])
  - Third Hall Play — "The King's Henchman,", 1929 May 17 (Box 72/73 [220_22])
  - Third Hall Play — "The King's Henchman,", 1929 May 17 (Box 72/73 [220_23])
  - Third Hall Play — "The King's Henchman,", 1929 May 17 (Box 72/73 [220_24])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Class of 1929 marching toward the Class of 1929's Tree Ceremonies, 1929 May 8 (Box 4 [Package021_005])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance given by the Class of 1931. Most participants are wearing stereotypical Native American costumes, 1929 May 8 (Box 4 [Package021_002])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance given by the Class of 1931. Most participants are wearing stereotypical Native American costumes, 1929 May 8 (Box 4 [Package021_003])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance given by the Class of 1931. Most participants are wearing stereotypical Native American costumes, 1929 May 8 (Box 4 [Package021_004])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance given by the Class of 1931. Most participants are wearing stereotypical Native American costumes, 1929 May 8 (Box 4 [Package021_008])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance given by the Class of 1931. Most participants are wearing stereotypical Native American costumes, 1929 May 8 (Box 7 [Package028_004])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance given by the Class of 1931. Most participants are wearing stereotypical Native American costumes, including Professor Herbert E. Mills, 1929 May 8 (Box 4 [Package021_001])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance given by the Class of 1931. Most participants are wearing stereotypical Native American costumes, including Professor Herbert E. Mills, 1929 May 8 (Box 4 [Package021_006])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance given by the Class of 1931. Most participants are wearing stereotypical Native American costumes, including Professor Herbert E. Mills, 1929 May 8 (Box 4 [Package021_007])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance given by the Class of 1931. Most participants are wearing stereotypical Native American costumes, including Professor Herbert E. Mills, 1929 May 8 (Box 7 [Package028_002])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance given by the Class of 1931. Most participants are wearing stereotypical Native American costumes, including Professor Herbert E. Mills, 1929 May 8 (Box 7 [Package028_003])
  - Sophomore Party — "Ring-Around-a-Rosie," a skit show presented by the Class of 1932 to the Class of 1933, 1929 Oct 19 (Box 56 [Package76_001])
  - Sophomore Party — "Ring-Around-a-Rosie," a skit show presented by the Class of 1932 to the Class of 1933, 1929 Oct 19 (Box 56 [Package76_002])
  - Sophomore Party — "Ring-Around-a-Rosie," a skit show presented by the Class of 1932 to the Class of 1933, 1929 Oct 19 (Box 56 [Package76_003])
  - Sophomore Party — "Ring-Around-a-Rosie," a skit show presented by the Class of 1932 to the Class of 1933, 1929 Oct 19 (Box 56 [Package76_004])
  - Sophomore Party — "Ring-Around-a-Rosie," a skit show presented by the Class of 1932 to the Class of 1933, 1929 Oct 19 (Box 56 [Package76_005])
  - Sophomore Party — "Ring-Around-a-Rosie," a skit show presented by the Class of 1932 to the Class of 1933, 1929 Oct 19 (Box 56 [Package76_006])
  - Sophomore Party — "Ring-Around-a-Rosie," a skit show presented by the Class of 1932 to the Class of 1933, 1929 Oct 19 (Box 56 [Package76_007])
  - Sophomore Party — "Ring-Around-a-Rosie," a skit show presented by the Class of 1932 to the Class of 1933, 1929 Oct 19 (Box 56 [Package76_008])
  - Sophomore Party — "Ring-Around-a-Rosie," a skit show presented by the Class of 1932 to the Class of 1933, 1929 Oct 19 (Box 56 [Package76_010])
  - Sophomore Party — "Ring-Around-a-Rosie," a skit show presented by the Class of 1932 to the Class of 1933, 1929 Oct 19 (Box 56 [Package76_011])
  - Sophomore Party — "Ring-Around-a-Rosie," a skit show presented by the Class of 1932 to the Class of 1933, 1929 Oct 19 (Box 56 [Package76_012])
  - Sophomore Party — Full cast of "Ring-Around-a-Rosie," a skit show presented by the Class of 1932 to the Class of 1933, 1929 Oct 19 (Box 56 [Package76_009])
  - Unidentified play — Unidentified production with stark sets and simple costumes, 1930s (Box 84 [Box240_021])
  - Unidentified play — Unidentified production with stark sets and simple costumes, 1930s (Box 87 [Box244_001])
  - Unidentified play — Unidentified production with stark sets and simple costumes, 1930s (Box 87 [Box244_002])
  - Unidentified play — Unidentified production with stark sets and simple costumes, 1930s (Box 87 [Box244_003])
  - Unidentified play — Unidentified production with stark sets and simple costumes, 1930s (Box 87 [Box244_004])
  - Unidentified play — Unidentified production with stark sets and simple costumes, 1930s (Box 87 [Box244_006])
  - Unidentified play — Unidentified production with stark sets and simple costumes, 1930s (Box 87 [Box244_007])
  - Unidentified play — Unidentified production with stark sets and simple costumes, 1930s (Box 87 [Box244_008])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 61/62 [200_14])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 31/32 [Box262_008])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 31/32 [Box262_009])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 31/32 [Box262_012])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 31/32 [Box262_013])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 31/32 [Box262_014])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 31/32 [Box262_015])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 31/32 [Box262_016])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 31/32 [Box262_017])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 31/32 [Box262_018])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 31/32 [Box262_019])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 32 [Box263_001])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 32 [Box263_017])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 32 [Box263_018])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 32 [Box263_024])
  - Second Hall Play — "The London Merchant or the History of George Barnwell,", 1930 Mar 15 (Box 32 [Box263_025])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1932, 1930 May (Box 6 [Package024_001])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1932, 1930 May (Box 6 [Package024_002])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1932, 1930 May (Box 6 [Package024_003])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1932, 1930 May (Box 6 [Package024_004])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1932, 1930 May (Box 6 [Package024_005])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1932, 1930 May (Box 8 [Package036_001])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1932, 1930 May (Box 8 [Package036_002])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1932, 1930 May (Box 8 [Package036_003])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1932, 1930 May (Box 8 [Package036_004])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1932, 1930 May (Box 8 [Package036_005])
  - Third Hall Play — "Monsieur Beaucaire,", 1930 May 17 (Box 74/75 [224_01])
  - Third Hall Play — "Monsieur Beaucaire,", 1930 May 17 (Box 74/75 [224_02])
  - Third Hall Play — "Monsieur Beaucaire,", 1930 May 17 (Box 74/75 [224_03])
  - Third Hall Play — "Monsieur Beaucaire,", 1930 May 17 (Box 74/75 [224_09])
  - Third Hall Play — "Monsieur Beaucaire,", 1930 May 17 (Box 74/75 [224_10])
  - Third Hall Play — "Monsieur Beaucaire,", 1930 May 17 (Box 74/75 [224_11])
  - Third Hall Play — "Monsieur Beaucaire,", 1930 May 17 (Box 74/75 [224_12])
  - Third Hall Play — "Monsieur Beaucaire,", 1930 May 17 (Box 74/75 [224_14])
  - Third Hall Play — "Monsieur Beaucaire,", 1930 May 17 (Box 74/75 [224_17])